Health insurance.
[Music]
So medical costume
Okay.
So
yes,
best insurance company insurance.
Best health plan
insurance.
Best companion health plan.
[Music]
First, best insurance company.
Claim settlement ratio. So
more than 30 insurance companies
insurance
claim settlement ratio. So climb
settlement ratio 100%.
But 99%
100%
insurance company
settlement ratio
99%
Okay.
So, client settlement ratio
more than 95%
point.
And then the companies
settlement
insurance
98% digital 97%
95%
of insurance.
So
no spam policy.
for
spam. Sorry. Spam
back
insurance.
So forceful
30 minutes.
Yes. Hospital network. So hospital
network
network companies network hospital.
So
hospital
insurance 11,500
star 14,000
16,400
hospital networks connection
product portfolio
So
health insurance.
So portfolio
and pre-existing
problem.
for
disease specific policies
[Music]
for checked
track record and customer feedback. So
last 10th
track
insurance
and reputation.
Fore
insurance.
Okay.
So government hospital,
private hospital.
So government insurance company.
So private companies also provide better
services.
insurance plan.
Number five, best insurance company.
Best insurance plan.
insurance.
So co- payment option
payment
insurance
payment option
insurance plan.
lecture
payment
insurance
room. So hospital
insurance plan
top to bottom.
So
room
Private room
waiting period
pre-existing
insurance.
So waiting period.
Okay.
So wait.
Pre
and post hospitalization charges.
60 days pre and post hospitalization
prehos
one of the process
insurance plan
pre and post hospitalization
and cashless
treatment
insurance.
So cash.
So
coverage on alternative treatment.
Sometimes
Okay.
So, alternative treatment
and low claim,
health insurance, health policy,
insurance plan.
No claim bonus
restoration benefit. Restoration
family
hospital.
So first hospital
second hospital
restoration
First of
Top three best insurance company and top
three best insurance health.
So top three companies
and
and best plans
just normal information.
So
health insurance
because
hospital
Boss, be the boss.